## **Bohdan Zaliskyi**

Project Manager

#### **Profile**

Project Manager specialist, working 4,5+ years in IT various innovative markets on Web, Mobile, VR/AR projects with international clients. Using Agile frameworks, more inclined to Management 3.0 style, have experience with version control services and project management tools, such as Atlassian Suite and other. Have non professional experience with Html, CSS, JS, React and C# (Unity3D).

### **Employment History**

## Project Manager/Business Analyst at LITSLINK, Kyiv

August 2017 - Present

Managing multiple Web, Mobile and VR (Unity3D) projects from various innovative markets: corporate, blockchain, VR/AR, dating, gaming, financial etc. Using Scrum, Kanban and Waterfall methodologies/ frameworks. Managing distributed teams across the globe, teams up to 10 specialists. Successful delivery of projects both short- and long-term with client's written positive review of work. Company "Project delivery of the year" award. PSM I certification obtained.

#### Web Project Manager at NAVI Design Lab, Kyiv

May 2016 - August 2017

Managing full cycle of web development in start-up digital company. PMBOK, Scrum/Agile. Managing different teams consisting from designers, frontend and backend developers, QA and copywriters. Developing documentation and wireframes with stakeholders and team from scratch and delivering final product within budget and timelines. Working with international clients, from Europe, USA, Japan, Dubai etc. Implementing Scrum framework in company from scratch.

#### **Details**

Kyiv, Ukraine, +380939340214 bogdanzaliskiy@gmail.com

Date / Place of birth 01/06/1993

Kyiv

**Skills** 

Planning

Negotiations

Problem Solving

Team Facilitation

Management

Analysis

Unity3D(C#)

HTML, CSS, JS

#### Languages

English

Russian

Ukrainian

Spanish

Web Project Manager at Maestro Ticket System, Kyiv

Managing development of business process automation system, custom web CMS and websites using CMSs. Successfully facilitating team consisting from 3 specialists: Designer, Fullstack Web developer, DevOps. Gathering requirements from stakeholders and writing specification documents.

#### **Education**

# Master's Degree, Project Management and Consulting, Kyiv National Economics UniversityKyiv

July 2014 – July 2015

Graduate work "Logistics enterprise development of business model" based on "Nova Poshta" company.

Jury board pick in III student scientific internet conference "Enterprise strategy: new generation of economists' view". Cases for companies Momondo "Travellenge" and Shell "Shell Ideas360".